Guide to the Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture records, 1954-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Architectural Records, 1954, circa 1960-1969 and undated (Box 38)
  - Thai Palace, R.C. Roof Construction at A, 20 of 20. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Temple, Ground Floor Plan, Plate No. 1. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 Sep 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Temple, Side Elevation, Plate No. 2. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 May 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Thai Temple, Cross Section A-A, Cross Section B-B, Plate No. 5. Panya-ngarm, Somchai. 1964 May 19. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC3, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Plan, 1 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Front Elevation, 2 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 19. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Side Envation [sic] and Section C-C, 3 of 8 and 4 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Section A-A, 5 of 8. Plue Chankeo. [1964 May]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Section B-B, 6 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Ceiling Decoration, 7 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 27. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Chapel Royal Temple, Detail of Ceiling Decoration, 8 of 8. Plue Chankeo. 1964 May 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Howard Wong's Drawings of 3 Buildings in 3 Scales. Howard Wong. undated. Tracing paper, Van Dyke print. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Plan of the Royal Pantheon. Plue Chankeo. 19[07] Jun 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Front Elevation of the Royal Pantheon. Plue Chankeo. undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC4, Box 31)
  - Site Plan from R.M. Towill, First Stage Only. R.M. Towill. 1964 Aug 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC5, Box 31)
  - Roof Details. Wong and Wong Architects. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC5, Box 31)
  - Servants Quarters for Estate of Miss Doris Duke. Y. Tom Makino, architect. 1968 Apr 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC6, Box 31)
  - Thai Residence for Foundation for Southeast Asia Art and Culture, No. 2/3, Front Elevation, Side Elevation. 1962 Nov 29. Photostat. (Opaperfolder SEAAC6, Box 31)
  - [Thai Residence for Foundation for Southeast Asia Art and Culture], Floor Plan. 1962 Nov 29. Photostat; positive photostat. (Opaperfolder SEAAC6, Box 31)
  - Thai Village-Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, Plan A-D, showing Bernice Bishop Estate, Sheet 1. undated. Diazo with colored ink. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC7, Box 31)
  - Thai Village-Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, Green Valley-Punaluu, Location of Plan "B" Dam Site, Sheet 2. undated. Diazo with colored ink. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC7, Box 31)
  - Thai Village-Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, Plan B, Sheet 3. undated. Diazo with colored ink. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC7, Box 31)
  - Thai Village-Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, Green Valley-Punaluu, Location of Plan "C" Village Sites, Sheet 4. undated. Diazo with colored ink. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC7, Box 31)
  - Thai Village-Foundation for Southeast Asian Art and Culture, Green Valley-Punaluu, Location of Plan "C" (closer detail, Sheet 5. undated. Diazo with colored ink. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC7, Box 31)
  - Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden Kahana Valley. Donald Wolbrink & Associates. 1966 Aug 12. Diazo. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC8, Box 31)
  - [Pacific Tropical Botanical Garden, Kahana Valley]. [Donald Wolbrink & Associates]. [1966]. Diazo. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC8, Box 31)
  - [Kahana Valley]. [Donald Wolbrink & Associates]. [1966 Aug]. Diazo. (Oversize-box Arch 3, Folder SEAAC8, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion at Hawaii USA, Sketch Plate 1, Sheets 1-4. Somchai Panya-ngarm. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC9, Box 31)
  - Thai Pavilion at Hawaii USA, Sketch Plate 2, Sheets 1-4. Somchai Panya-ngarm. 1963 Jul 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC9, Box 31)
  - Cross Section of Side Elevation, 7 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 [Nov 8]. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC9, Box 31)
  - Cross Section Front Elevation, 6 of 10. Chareon Seng Thai Limited Partnership/Writer, Pleu Chankoo/Copy by Chumhong Lohitkoopt. 1964 Aug 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder SEAAC9, Box 31)